sign-up.to 2011-03-18

# Privacy Policy | Sign-Up.to

We take the privacy of client and end user data very seriously. The entire Sign-Up.to system is designed to provide all parties with complete control over their data.

We believe that your personal data is your own, and you should control it. Because of this Sign-Up.to do not rent, sell or otherwise disclose data to 3rd parties unless we are required to by law. 

As a subscriber to a company who uses Sign-Up.to you have complete access to data stored on you - simply log in at [http://subscriber.sign-up.to](http://subscriber.sign-up.to/) and you can view, edit and delete your data completely free of charge.

That's the short version. Because our lawyers like to earn their fees, they insisted that we also have the long version below...

Sign-Up Technologies Limited (referred to in this Privacy Policy as "SuTL", "we", "us" or "our") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how we use the information we collect about you through Sign-UpT, how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy. This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms of Use 

**1\. Contact details**

The Sign-Up website (the "Site") and the Sign-Up data processing services (together, the "Services") are provided by Sign-Up Technologies Limited, a company registered in England and Wales with company registration number 04674316\. 

**Registered Office:** Sign-Up Technologies Limited, 60 Maltings Place, Fulham, London SW6 2BX, UK.   
**Contact Address:** 60 Maltings Place, Fulham, London SW6 2BX.   
**e-mail:**[solutions@sign-up.to ](mailto:solutions@sign-up.to)  

**2\. Introduction**

2.1 We are registered under, and process personal data in accordance with, the United Kingdom's data protection laws.   
2.2 This Privacy Policy covers the provision of the Services only and not any other companies' websites which you may access from the Site or by using the Services.   
2.3 If we change the Privacy Policy we will place notices on the Site and post the changes on this page. If you do not accept any changes to the Privacy Policy please stop using the Services and close your membership account. 

**3\. Personal Information Collected**

3.1 We will only collect personal information about you that you have given, either:   
(a) when you register for the Services; or   
(b) if you have previously registered your details with a company which has since joined the Sign-Up Services.   
3.2 When you register to use the Services you will be asked to provide personal information such as your name, postal and e-mail addresses, contact telephone numbers, date of birth, gender and other lifestyle information. 

**4\. Use of personal Information**

4.1 We may use personal information for: administrative, operational and marketing purposes and to communicate with you about your use of the Services any changes to the Services. We will only pass on your information to other companies if it is necessary to perform the Services or with your prior consent. Those companies may contact you to inform you of their services and products. Any personal information that you choose to provide to us or to other companies using our Services will only be used in support of the intended purposes stated at the time at which it was collected and subject to any preferences indicated by you.   
4.2 If you breach the Terms of Use your personal information may be passed to third parties, such as our legal advisors to the extent necessary to enable those third parties to resolve the matter.   
4.3 If this business is sold or integrated with another business, your details may be disclosed to our advisors and any prospective purchasers and their advisors and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.   
4.4 We may be obliged to disclose your personal information if required to do so by law. 

**5\. Other Information**

5.1 We may also collect and disclose information to third parties in aggregate (so that no individual members are identified) for statistical analysis and strategic development purposes. 

**6\. Cookies**

6.1 We may use "cookies" to collect aggregate information. A "Cookie" is a small piece of information sent by our web server to your web browser, which enables us to record anonymous details and allows you to move around the Site faster. We may use cookies for a number of purposes, for instance to enable us to simplify the logging on process, to help ensure the security and authenticity of members and to enable traffic monitoring. You can find out more about the way cookies work on [http://www.cookiecentral.com ](http://www.cookiecentral.com/).   
6.2 Most browsers allow you to turn off the cookie function. If you want to know how to do this, please look at the help menu on your browser. However, if you turn off the cookie function your use of the Services may be impaired. 

**7\. Overseas**

7.1 We will only pass on information about you as an individual (as opposed to aggregate information) to third parties overseas to enable us to perform services requested by you.   
7.2 Owing to the global nature of the Internet, the information you provide may be transferred in transit to countries outside the European Economic Area that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this policy. However, we do our best to ensure that your personal information is secure. 

**8\. Security**

8.1 As required by under UK data protection laws, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given to us, to prevent unauthorised access. We use industry standard technology to encrypt your personal information. However, the Internet is not a secure environment and we cannot guarantee the security of any information which you send to us. 

**9\. Other websites**

9.1 Our Site may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other websites using the links provided, the operators of these websites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy practices, which may differ from ours. 

9.2 This site uses a tool that collects your requests for pages and passes elements of them to search engines to assist them in indexing this site. We control the configuration of the tool and are responsible for any information sent to the search engines.

**10\. Updating your details**

10.1 If you wish to update any of your personal details at any time, for example if you change your e-mail address, or you do not wish to receive information about a particular product or service, or if you wish to close your membership account, please update your membership details as instructed on the Site and your details will be updated as soon as is reasonably practicable.   
10.2 If you delete your account, other companies with which you have registered via the Services may continue to process your data but they should not contact you without your consent. 

**11\. Access rights**

11.1 You have a right to access the personal data that is held about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information we hold about you, please write to: Privacy Officer, Sign-Up Technologies Limited, 60 Maltings Place, London, SW6 2BX, UK, enclosing a cheque for £10 payable to Sign-Up Technologies Limited to cover our administration costs.   
When writing to us, please state your name, postal address and mobile phone number and provide brief details of the information that you require. 

**12\. Contact us**

If you would like to contact us with any queries or comments on our privacy practices, please write to the contact address above or send an e-mail to [solutions@sign-up.to](mailto:solutions@sign-up.to)
